

JOHAN **MEDINA**

Portfolio online: bit.ly/JMdesigner

CONTACT



(+57) 316 532 5256

isebastianm1113@gmail.com

FOLLOW ME

Bē behance.net/jsebastianfa54

in bit.ly/linkedinJohanM

github.com/johan1113

LANGUAGES

ESPAÑOL: Native

INGLÉS: B2

TOOLS

JavaScript CSS & SCSS

React NextJS

Github Firebase

Mongo DB Slack

Asana Figma

Adobe Suite Wordpress

Styled Components

ABC

ABOUT ME

I am an interactive media design student with experience in planning, executing and developing digital products through design; achieving high levels of innovation in the market through *front-end development*, *user experience design* and *user interface design*.

Thanks to my studies, I have developed leadership skills, project management, effective communication, group work and active learning. All this has facilitated my ability to lead and / or be part of innovation projects in competent companies.



EDUCATION

> Interactive Media Design

Aug 2015 - Nowadays

Universidad Icesi, Santiago de Cali, Colombia

5th Year Student.



EXPERIENCE

> Front-End Developer with React

Jul. 2020 - Nowadays

Angular Diseño más Interacción - Internship

Apprentice as a React developer, in charge of developing web solutions with high standards of development quality, and high fidelity in interaction and user interface design of the product.

> UI Designer and Wordpress Developer

Aug. 2019 - Mar. 2020

Angular Diseño más Interacción

In charge of the design and construction of user interface content for commercial web pages, and development of web platforms with Wordpress.

> UI Designer and Wordpress Developer

Jun. 2019 - Aug. 2019

A Creative Work

Responsible for the design of user interfaces for commercial web pages and development of web platforms with Wordpress.

> Academic Consultant - Programming

Sept. 2018 - Jun. 2019

Universidad Icesi

Advisor in the development of digital products with tools such as Java, Javascript, CSS, HTML, Android, Arduino and React. In charge of providing support to all Interactive Media Design Students on algorithm programming and implementation strategies.



SKILLS

FRONT-END DEVELOPMENT ACTIVE LEARNING

UI DEVELOPMENT TEAMWORK

UI DESIGN ORIENTATION TO PROBLEM SOLVING

UX DESIGN ACTIVE LISTENING